<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Vacancies>

<Vacancy>
<Individual>Annabel Tipp</Individual>
<ContactEmail>a.tipp.7169BF287.0@applythis.net</ContactEmail>
<CreatedDate>2018-02-02 02:40:40</CreatedDate>
<Reference>2051A</Reference>
<Title>Project Manager</Title>
 <JobType>Contract</JobType>
<Industry>Information Technology</Industry>
<Location>Cheshire, Cheshire</Location>
<Salary>£375 - 400 per day</Salary>
<StartDate>2018-02-12</StartDate>
<IsHidden>TRUE</IsHidden>
<JobDescription>&lt;p&gt;Project Manager &amp;ndash; GDPR&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3 Months contract +&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;pound;400pd&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cheshire&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am currently working on behalf of a leading organisation based in Cheshire who are currently looking to bring on a contractor resource to assist with their work around GDPR. The business has been busy over the last few months putting together their GDPR plans and are now looking for a seasoned PM with experience of managing a GDPR project to come in and assist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll be&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing the project deliverables to plan, within budget, on time and to the required level&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proactively monitoring tracking and progress&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Managing risk and issues within the project&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ongoing alignment of the project with business and IS requirements&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Liaison with the Programme Manager, PMO Manager and/or other Project Managers as appropriate, to ensure that work is neither overlooked nor duplicated&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Establish relevant frameworks for completing the gap/risk analysis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a fantastic opportunity for a project manager with specific experience working within the GDPR space. If you are currently looking for a contract and are available relatively soon, please get in touch as a matter of urgency.&lt;/p&gt;</JobDescription>
</Vacancy>

<Vacancy>
<Individual>Tim Johnson</Individual>
<ContactEmail>t.johnson.616A8E236.0@applythis.net</ContactEmail>
<CreatedDate>2018-02-06 04:38:38</CreatedDate>
<Reference>2062</Reference>
<Title>Business Analyst</Title>
 <JobType>Permanent</JobType>
<Industry>Information Technology</Industry>
<Location>Hereford, Herefordshire</Location>
<Salary>Market related</Salary>
<StartDate>2018-03-05</StartDate>
<IsHidden>TRUE</IsHidden>
<JobDescription>&lt;p&gt;An experienced Business&amp;nbsp;Analyst who has a analytical&amp;nbsp;mindset is required for a permanenet contract. You will ideally have experience within&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; e-commerce working in a very agile environment.&amp;nbsp;You will be pro-active with a strong desire to work to a continuous improvement methodology. My client will provide ongoing training and support and are looking for candidates who want to progress and implement positive change to current practices.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Client:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An e-commerce retailer, who have an international brand&amp;nbsp;and work closely with online giant Google, have arranged&amp;nbsp;consistent growth plans for 2018. They are looking to expand their Business Analyst&amp;nbsp;team, meaning you will be providing full lifecycle analysis across the full lifecycle process. The ultimate aim of the team is to ensure all analysis is completed, whether it be initial analysis at Epic level,&amp;nbsp;as part of an Agile team at User story level or any other business change.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The large, open plan office is less than 10&amp;nbsp;minutes walk from the train station with a team of fifty, all operating in a very agile environment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The culture is one that promotes a forward thinking and progressive approach but still maintains a laid back, dress down demeanor. The senior management are open to new ideas and at times, provide the team with new approaches and ideas themselves.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Succesful Business&amp;nbsp;Analyst:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytical and problem solving approach and mindset&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good business ingenuity and awareness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in a B.A. role for a minimum of two years across different projects&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A drive and determination to complete tasks and deliver business value&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills with an ability to interpret technical issues and translate them into a language understood at all levels of competence&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Confident and assertive in their decision making process, with the abilty to laise with stakeholders at all levels.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Passion to devlop your own skill set and progress&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Agile approach with a desire to improve current approaches and put them into practice&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Role:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full lifecycle analysis throughout business change&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The ability to provide continuous improvement, by effectively obtaining both functional and non-functional requirements and&amp;nbsp;recording, refining and communicating requirements ensuring effective business change is carried out&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensuring User Stories are structured and written to a standard that will allow the delivery of a feasible business product&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Delivering business needs via &quot;minimum viable product&quot; principles with a minimal spend maximum benefit approach&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work alongside Google staff members with&amp;nbsp;occasional&amp;nbsp;Google office visits&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working in an Agile Environment with open communication across teams&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop and build relationships throughout the business and with external parties of all levels, with the vision&amp;nbsp;to deliver a proactive and credible solution&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Implementing &quot;continuous improvement&quot; methodology to provide best practice, with aim to maximise productivity and effectiveness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Attending meetings as a representative of the company&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Attending relevant training to ensure progression of your skill set&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The role is commutable Gloucester, Worcester, Cheltenham, Abergavenny and surrounding areas.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are an experienced Business&amp;nbsp;Analyst, who works to a continuous improvement methodology,&amp;nbsp;have worked in an Agile environment,&amp;nbsp;have excellent communication skills and&amp;nbsp;a&amp;nbsp;forward thinking approach,&amp;nbsp;then don't hesitate, click the link below to apply.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</JobDescription>
</Vacancy>

<Vacancy>
<Individual>Tim Johnson</Individual>
<ContactEmail>t.johnson.116AB4101.0@applythis.net</ContactEmail>
<CreatedDate>2018-02-07 09:52:52</CreatedDate>
<Reference>2065</Reference>
<Title>Web Developer </Title>
 <JobType>Permanent</JobType>
<Industry>Information Technology</Industry>
<Location>Hereford, Herefordshire</Location>
<Salary>Market related</Salary>
<StartDate>2018-03-05</StartDate>
<IsHidden>TRUE</IsHidden>
<JobDescription>&lt;p&gt;Are you looking for your next challenge as a Web Developer? The successful web developer will be responsible for developing website and services to a very high standard. You'll be involved in the Tech. design and work within a very skilled development team. Working with Business Analysts, technical leads, and an experienced testing team in an incredibly agile environment. You will be working with them on the creation and review of User stories to include acceptance criteria.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Client: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An E-commerce retailer, who have an international brand and work closely with online giant Google, have arranged consistent growth plans for 2018. They are looking to expand their Development team, in particular for this role, Web Development. The ultimate aim of the team is to ensure the website code is developed and improved from scratch at times but also by editing and modification of existing code. Across six platforms, the website is the key to the business, allowing customers to view, order and return products with ease. The website must be seamless with ease of use and the marketing functions being key functions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The large, open plan office is less than a 10 minute walk from the train station with a team of fifty, all operating in a very agile environment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The culture is one that promotes a forward thinking and progressive approach but still maintains a laid back, dress down demeanour. The senior management are open to new ideas and at times, provide the team with new approaches and ideas themselves, with Senior Management being in the same office and open to communication. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Successful Web Developer: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with .NET, C# and API's&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fully capable of developing web applications and services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience Developing in a cloud environment &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good communication and team working skills. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Capable of working to deadlines &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Organised, proactive and efficient time management. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Two years or more experience in developing websites using the full Software Development Lifecycle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Role: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improving Website through the Development of the code base by editing and modifying the current code or creating new code. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Structure Analysis to make sure the 100% unit test in JavaScript is completed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coding standards and principles must be followed through peer review of code and content adaptations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Developed features are produced to a high standard in an efficient and calculated manner. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Full SDLC is followed throughout. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expectation to keep up to date with current, and learn new technologies &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Training courses are provided for the purpose of continued personal development &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The role is commutable Gloucester, Worcester, Cheltenham, Abergavenny and surrounding areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Generous salary offered along with company bonus, healthcare, childcare and huge discounts of their products.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are an experienced Web Developer, with the desire to ensure 100% user friendly websites are delivered, have worked in an Agile environment, have excellent communication skills and a forward thinking approach, then don't hesitate, click the link below to apply.&lt;/p&gt;</JobDescription>
</Vacancy>

<Vacancy>
<Individual>Tim Johnson</Individual>
<ContactEmail>t.johnson.416ABAFE4.0@applythis.net</ContactEmail>
<CreatedDate>2018-02-07 10:37:37</CreatedDate>
<Reference>2066</Reference>
<Title>UI Developer </Title>
 <JobType>Permanent</JobType>
<Industry>Information Technology</Industry>
<Location>Shropshire, Shropshire</Location>
<Salary>Market related</Salary>
<StartDate>2018-03-05</StartDate>
<IsHidden>TRUE</IsHidden>
<JobDescription>&lt;p&gt;Are you an experienced UI Web Developer looking for your next challenge? The successful UI web developer will be responsible for the User Interface aspect of the website and functions&amp;nbsp;to a very high standard. You'll be involved in the technical&amp;nbsp;design and work within a very skilled development team. Working alongside&amp;nbsp;business analysts, technical leads, and an experienced testing team in an incredibly agile environment. You will be working with them on the creation and review of stories to include acceptance criteria.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The Client:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An E-commerce retailer, who have an international brand and work closely with online giant Google, have arranged consistent growth plans for 2018. They are looking to expand their Development team, in particular for this role, UI Web Development. The ultimate aim of the team is to ensure the website code is developed and improved from scratch at times but also by editing and modification of existing code. Across six platforms at present, with a strong aim to expand,&amp;nbsp;the website is the key to the business, allowing customers to view, order and return products with ease. The User Interface must be seamless with smooth ease of use being&amp;nbsp;essential.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; The large, open plan office is less than a 10 minute walk from the train station with a team of fifty, all operating in a very agile environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The culture is one that promotes a forward thinking and progressive approach but still maintains a laid back, dress down demeanour. The senior management are open to new ideas and at times, provide the team with new approaches and ideas themselves, with senior management being in the same office and open to communication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Successful UI Web Developer:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with CSS and Bootstrap&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with HTML and HTML5&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Using and developing JavaScript and jQuery is essential&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience of .NET,&amp;nbsp;C# and WebAPI's&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knockout or Angular experience&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Familiar with browser tests and de-bugging&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Confident and communicative in a team environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Two years of experience in developing websites using the full software development lifecycle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Analytical and driven towards&amp;nbsp;the end result.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proactive and organised time management skills&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Capable of working under pressure to tight deadlines.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Role:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improving Website through the Development of the code base by editing and modifying the current code or creating new code, with an aim to make sure high quality graphics and brand consistency is delivered.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Structure Analysis to make sure the 100% unit test in JavaScript is completed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Working alongside E-commerce team to ensure website optimisation and usability is created for&amp;nbsp;the end user.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The team follow best practice&amp;nbsp;for accessibility and cross-browser compatibility&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coding standards and principles must be followed through peer review of code and content adaptations&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Identification of&amp;nbsp;functional, technical or performance issues and&amp;nbsp;providing&amp;nbsp;solutions and suggestions for improvements is expected.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Full SDLC is followed throughout.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Expectation to keep up to date with current, and learn new technologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Training courses are provided for the purpose of continued personal development&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The role is commutable Gloucester, Worcester, Cheltenham, Abergavenny and surrounding areas.&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Generous salary available for the successful candidate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are an experienced Web Developer, with the desire to ensure 100% user friendly websites are delivered, have worked in an Agile environment, have excellent communication skills and a forward thinking approach, then don't hesitate, click the link below to apply.&lt;/p&gt;</JobDescription>
</Vacancy>

<Vacancy>
<Individual>Tim Johnson</Individual>
<ContactEmail>t.johnson.716AE2767.0@applythis.net</ContactEmail>
<CreatedDate>2018-02-07 01:03:03</CreatedDate>
<Reference>2067</Reference>
<Title>Senior Developer </Title>
 <JobType>Permanent</JobType>
<Industry>Information Technology</Industry>
<Location>Hereford, Herefordshire</Location>
<Salary>Market related</Salary>
<StartDate>2018-03-05</StartDate>
<IsHidden>TRUE</IsHidden>
<JobDescription>&lt;p&gt;My client is looking for an experienced Senior Developer, responsible for developing all aspects of website, applications and services to the highest quality. You will be responsible for developing new code as well as modifying existing code&amp;nbsp;within a&amp;nbsp;Scrum team. The successful Senior Developer will have good management skills and a strong ability to mentor and develop fellow team members. Working in a very Agile environment alongside Business Analysts, technical leads, developers and QA analysts to create and review stories and features.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; &amp;nbsp;My client will provide ongoing training and support and are looking for candidates who want to progress and implement positive change and adhere to current practices.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Client:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An E-commerce retailer, who have an international brand&amp;nbsp;and work closely with online giant Google, have arranged&amp;nbsp;consistent growth plans for 2018. They are looking to expand their Development&amp;nbsp;team, and actively recruiting for a Senior Developer.&amp;nbsp;The ultimate aim of the team is to ensure that coding is created in the most efficient way; the teams are working to the best methods and practices, communicating effectively and are mentored and motivated to complete&amp;nbsp;tasks&amp;nbsp;to deadline.&amp;nbsp;The end result will ensure that the E-commerce function is user friendly, the user journey is faultless, kept&amp;nbsp;up to date, and works alongside all relevant other departments such as marketing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The large, open plan office is less than 10&amp;nbsp;minutes&amp;rsquo; walk from the train station with a team of 50 all operating in a very agile environment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The culture is one that promotes a forward thinking and progressive approach but still maintains a laid back, dress down demeanour. The senior management are open to new ideas and at times, provide the team with new approaches and ideas themselves. Management&amp;nbsp;at all levels are accessible to communicate with and appreciate suggestions and input from all members of the team.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Successful Senior Developer:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced in asynchrous processes,&amp;nbsp;multi-threaded&amp;nbsp;execution and scaling&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;E-commerce experience using TDD and BDD and developing with complete&amp;nbsp;test coverage&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;Detailed knowledge of Devops functions with the ability to deploy monitor and troubleshoot issues relating to the operational performance of configuration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to consider operational requirements when developing solutions&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to design data schemes for relational database or object stores and understanding when to use each.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Development of mocked or stubbed services and a good understanding of their usage.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Confident and communicative in an agile team environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum&amp;nbsp;of 12 months experience in a commercial environment, involving full software development lifecycle, (web based solutions) and testing teams that involve Automated test and Selenium tools&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Full understanding of 10 oWasp principles&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of encryption within .NET and Cloud and understanding when to utilise them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proactive and organised time management skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Capable of working under pressure to tight deadlines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tools and Technology:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;CSS, HTML and Javascript for creation and maintenance of websites&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Javascript libraries&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CSS libraries&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;C# with windows applications or windows services&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;C# with entity framework, LINQ, MSMQ and integration with stored procedure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;C# to create API's&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SQL server&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NoSQL database&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Role:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The company will expect an advanced understanding of the Agile methodology and the ability to decide best use of Agile or Waterfall methods.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to perform training on agile processes if necessary&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Capability of communicating effectively with the team at senior level, ensuring they are being mentored and enhancing development of the team wherever necessary&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The ability to motivate the team to perform to deadlines, taking into account interests and competency of the team. This will involve an empathetic, communicative approach, tailored to suit each team&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The ability to communicate complex technical data and issues in a clear manner across all functions and experience levels of the business&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Making sure you and the team are following development standards and principles, have a good working knowledge of &amp;nbsp;industry standard practice, SDLC and good understanding of principles around configuration encryption and security&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Perform peer review performance on code ensuring security and development principles and practice are being followed, a decent knowledge of CI/CD, and capable of maintaining, building and releasing any component to any environment to include trouble shooting when required&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ownership of the development principles, ensuring principles are followed through the development community, have a good knowledge of automation and can troubleshoot tasks relating to continuous integration and continuous delivery&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to provide input into planning of how duties are to be carried out, what technologies are to be used and what security principles are to be applied&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Taking&amp;nbsp;a lead role in the technical direction of the development team making sure team are aware of good software design and development principles&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Desire to learn new technologies, methods, best practice, and self-development and encourage this throughout the team&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop and build relationships throughout the business and with external parties of all levels, with the vision&amp;nbsp;to deliver a proactive and credible solution&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Attending meetings as a representative of the company&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Attending relevant training to ensure progression of your skill set&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The role is commutable Gloucester, Worcester, Cheltenham, Abergavenny and surrounding areas.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt; &lt;br /&gt; Excellent salary available for the successful candidate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are an experienced Senior Developer who works to a continuous improvement methodology,&amp;nbsp;have worked in an Agile environment,&amp;nbsp;have excellent communication skills and&amp;nbsp;a&amp;nbsp;forward thinking approach,&amp;nbsp;then don't hesitate, click the link below to apply.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</JobDescription>
</Vacancy>

<Vacancy>
<Individual>Tim Johnson</Individual>
<ContactEmail>t.johnson.216AE2372.0@applythis.net</ContactEmail>
<CreatedDate>2018-02-07 12:58:58</CreatedDate>
<Reference>2068</Reference>
<Title>Senior QA Analyst </Title>
 <JobType>Permanent</JobType>
<Industry>Information Technology</Industry>
<Location>Hereford, Herefordshire</Location>
<Salary>Market related</Salary>
<StartDate>2018-03-12</StartDate>
<IsHidden>False</IsHidden>
<JobDescription>&lt;p&gt;An experienced Senior&amp;nbsp;QA Analyst, experienced&amp;nbsp;on E-commerce Web platforms is required for my Client who are growing year on year. You will hold responsibility for the analysis and high quality level of code. Working within&amp;nbsp;the delivery team the successful senior QA will be responsible for improving analysis. You will also work alongside business analysts, technical leads and testers to test and review acceptance criteria.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Client:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An E-commerce retailer, who have an international brand and work closely with online giant Google, have arranged some consistent growth plans for 2018. The Senior QA will be making sure the technical direction of the QA team is being correctly followed, in line with good software and design principles.&amp;nbsp;The ultimate aim of the team is to provide a safe and user friendly platform that potential customers can use with ease.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They are heading towards a more fully automated environment with the end goal being 90% automation to 10% manual. They operate in a fully agile environment and use their own bespoke tools alongside SQL which is much used throughout the teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The large, open plan office is less than 10&amp;nbsp;minutes&amp;rsquo; walk from the train station. The whole team is 50 strong, with the successful candidate working alongside&amp;nbsp;an agile team of six to seven testers and one senior developer.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The culture is one that promotes a forward thinking and progressive approach but still maintains a laid back, dress down demeanour. The senior management are open to new ideas and at times, provide the team with new approaches and ideas themselves.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Successful Senior QA Analyst:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have good experience of Automation tests and framework including load, stress and performance testing plus script automation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience testing within a cloud infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience of Retail, E-commerce, or other commercial environment in a multi-channel capacity; with a good understanding of technologies and tools associate with this environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A good track record of delivering software deployments&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Confident enough in your ability to&amp;nbsp;challenge any processes to make sure you deliver quality delivery&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Driven by results with a strong motivation to reach the end goal&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Confident and communicative in a team environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Two years of experience in executing&amp;nbsp;Agile QA processes tools and techniques&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proactive and organised time management skills&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Capable of working under pressure to tight deadlines.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Flexible in your approach with a strong desire to learn new methods and technology and the ability to motivate the team to have the same desire.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tools and Technology required:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gherkin/Specflow&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Jira Agile&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HTML&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SQL Queries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Role:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensuring QA standards and principles are being followed by peer performance review of tests and criteria&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Making sure features produced by the team are high quality,&amp;nbsp;in an efficient manner and that is continued throughout future process&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Follow a fully Agile Software Development Lifecycle&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop and mentor QA community to include one to one mentoring if needed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Improving quality of code to make sure the team operates at 100% test coverage&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Identify any&amp;nbsp;functional, technical or performance problems and create suggestion for improvements&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Proactive and organised time management skills&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Attend training to develop and enhance current skills as well as learn new skills and technology&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Attend internal and external meetings as a representative of the company&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The role is commutable Gloucester, Worcester, Cheltenham, Abergavenny and surrounding areas.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excellent Salary Available after succesful one stage interview.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are an experienced QA Analyst with knowledge of implementing Automated tests across E-commerce platforms, have worked in an Agile environment in a similar industry, are forward thinking, enjoy learning new tech and would like to learn more about Google Analytics and the processes behind it. Then don't hesitate, click the link below to apply.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</JobDescription>
</Vacancy>
</Vacancies>